A Guide to the Papers of the Dean of Students, ca. 1968-1970, 1980-2005
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series V: Files of Glenna C. Chang, Assistant Dean for Asian Pacific American Programs
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Graduate Information Sheets 2000-2001 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Graduate Information Sheets 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Handouts n.d. (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Holiday Party 1999 (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Original Letters, Applications, Brochures, Etc. 1999 (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Packet for Peer Advisors 1999 (Box-folder 27:8)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Peer Advising Program (Asian Pacific Americans) 1999 (Box-folder 27:9)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Peer Advisor Applications 2000-2001 (Box-folder 27:10)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Peer Advisor Applications 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27:11)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Reservations 1999 (Box-folder 27:12)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Sample Packet 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27:13)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Selections Committee 1999-2000 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Peer Advisors Summer Information 2000-2001 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Training Information n.d. (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Training Material n.d. (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--T-shirts 2000 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Research 1998-1999 (Box-folder 28:6)
  - State Council for Higher Education for Virginia 2001 (Box-folder 28:7)
  - The United 1999 (Box-folder 28:8)
  - Voices of the Past 2000 (Box-folder 28:9)
  - Working for an Asian American Studies Program 2000-2001 (Box-folder 28:10)
  - Work in Progress--Asian Student Union 2000 (Box-folder 28:11)
  - Work in Progress--Charting Diversity 2000 (Box-folder 28:12)
  - Work in Progress--Chinese Student Association 1998-2000 (Box-folder 28:13)
  - Work in Progress--15% Committee Asians and Asian Americans 2000 (Box-folder 28:14)
  - Work in Progress--Cultural Programming Board 1999 (Box-folder 28:15)
  - Work in Progress--Grounds for Discussion 2000 (Box-folder 28:16)
  - Work in Progress--Miscellaneous 2000 (Box-folder 28:17)
  - Work in Progress--Peer Advising and Family Network 2000-2001 (Box-folder 28:18)
  - Work in Progress--Peer Advising and Family Network--Early Move-ins 2000 (Box-folder 28:19)
  - Work in Progress--Peer Advising and Family Network--Faculty/Staff Network Information Sheets 2000 (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Work in Progress--Peer Advising and Family Network--Originals and Advisor/Advisees Mailing Information 2000 (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Work in Progress--Peer Advising and Family Network--Retreat 2000 (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Work in Progress--Room Reservations 2000 (Box-folder 29:4)
- Series VI: Files of Ajay T. Nair, Assistant Dean of Students for Asian Pacific American Students
  - AMEL 302--Topics in Asian America--Lectures 2002 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - AMEL 302--Topics in Asian America--Change Projects 2002 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - AMEL 302--Topics in Asian America--Change Projects 2002 (Box-folder 29:7)
  - AMEL 302--Topics in Asian America--Change Projects 2002 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month 2002 May-2003 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month 2001-2002 Apr (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute 2000-2001 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--2001-2002 2002 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Applications 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Applications 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Applications 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Applications 2000 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Letters, Lists, Intergenerational Meeting 2000-2001 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Networking Meeting Faculty and Administration List and Letter 2000-2001 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Nominations 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Nominations Letters 2000-2001 (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Nomination Requests 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:7)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Nominees List and Letter 2000-2001 (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Session Evaluations--Session 1 2001 Dec (Box-folder 31:9)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Session Evaluations--Session 3 2002 Feb 7 (Box-folder 31:10)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Session Evaluations--Session 4 2002 Feb 21 (Box-folder 31:11)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Spring 2001 (Box-folder 31:12)
  - Asian Student Union--Summer 2000 (Box-folder 31:13)
  - Diapason Retreat Registrations 2002-2003 (Box-folder 31:14)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:15)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Contacts 2001 (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Expense Sheets 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Miscellaneous 2001 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Original Applications 2001 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Retreat 2001 (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Summer Mailing 2001 (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--T-shirt 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:9)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Updates 2001 (Box-folder 32:10)
- Series VII: Files of Ajay T. Nair and Daisy P. Rodriguez, Assistant Dean for Asian Pacific American Students
  - Asian American Student Concerns 1993-1994 (Box-folder 32:11)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute 2004 (Box-folder 32:12)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute 2002-2003 (Box-folder 32:13)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute 2000-2001 (Box-folder 32:14)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Facilitators 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:15)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Ideas n.d. (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Readings 2002-2003 (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Selection Materials 2002-2003 (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Asian Pacific American LEAD Retreat 2002 (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Asian Student Union--A Multifaceted Proposal 1995-1996 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Asian Student Union--Five Year Plan 1994-1995 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - DiAPAson 2004 (Box-folder 33:7)
  - DiAPAson 2003 (Box-folder 33:8)
  - DiAPAson 2002 (Box-folder 33:9)
  - DiAPAson--Binder Contents 2002 (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Multicultural Center n.d. (Box-folder 33:11)
  - Office of African-American Affairs--Mentoring Program 1998-1999 (Box-folder 33:12)
  - Office of African-American Affairs and Office of Career Planning and Placement--Workshop Series 1999-2001 (Box-folder 33:13)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 2002 Sep-2003 (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 2002 Apr-Sep (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Advisors 2002-2003 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Advisors/Executive Board 2003-2004 (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Banquet 2003 (Box-folder 34:6)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Budget 2002-2003 (Box-folder 34:7)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Executive Board Applications 2004-2005 (Box-folder 34:8)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Executive Board Training and Interviews (Advisors) 2003 (Box-folder 34:9)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Executive Retreat 2002 (Box-folder 34:10)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Interviews 2002-2003 (Box-folder 34:11)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Notes and Agendas 2003-2004 (Box-folder 34:12)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Poplar Ridge 2001-2002 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Reservations 2003 (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Retreat 2003 (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Retreat Evaluations 2002 (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Spring Training 2003 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Summer Mailing 2003-2004 (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Summer Training 2003 (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--University Wide Mentoring Meeting 2003 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - South Asian Leaders Retreat 2002 (Box-folder 35:9)
  - Student Survey--Research 1999 (Box-folder 35:10)
  - University Environmental Study of Asian Americans 1993-1996 (Box-folder 35:11)
- Series VIII: Restricted
  - Asian American Student Conference 1999 (Box-folder 36:1)
    pulled from files of Glenna C. Chang
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Applications--Accepted, Rejected, Letters 2002 (Box-folder 36:2)
    pulled from files of Ajay T. Nair
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Applications 2002 (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Nominations Letters 2000 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Selection Material 2002-2003 (Box-folder 36:5)
    pulled from files of Ajay T. Nair and Daisy P. Rodriguez
  - Asian Pacific American Parents Association--Letter and Applications 2001 (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Award--In Honor of Ernie Ern 2000 (Box-folder 36:7)
    pulled from files of Robert T. Canevari
  - Award--In Honor of Ernie Ern 1999 (Box-folder 36:8)
  - Award--In Honor of Ernie Ern 1994-2000 (Box-folder 36:9)
  - Blagden, Gus Committee 1999-2001 (Box-folder 36:10)
  - Blagden, Gus Nominations 1999 (Box-folder 36:11)
  - Budgets--Office of Dean of Students, Resident Life Office 1998 (Box-folder 36:12)
  - General Counsel 1995-2000 (Box-folder 36:13)
  - Gray-Carrington Committee 1997-1999 (Box-folder 36:14)
  - Judiciary Committee 1998-1999 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Leadership Seminar--Hispanic/Native American 1994 (Box-folder 37:2)
    pulled from files of Pablo J. Davis
  - Miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Advisee Applications 2001 (Box-folder 37:4)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Advisee Applications 1999 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Advisee Applications--Follow-Up 2001 (Box-folder 37:6)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Applications 2003-2004 (Box-folder 37:7)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Applications 2003-2004 (Box-folder 37:8)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Executive Board Applicatio 2002-2003 (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Expense Sheets 2002 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Housing Applications 1999 (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Summer Mailing 2003 (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Peer Mentoring Program n.d. (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Recommendations Other Than Students 1997-2000 (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Residence Life--Hereford College (New College) 1996 (Box-folder 38:7)
  - Residence Life Office 1998 (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Search Committee: Assistant Dean of Students--Hispanic, Latino 1998 (Box-folder 38:9)
  - Search Committee: Assistant Dean--Resident Life Office 1999 (Box-folder 38:10)
  - (Vice President for) Student Affairs 1997-1998 (Box-folder 38:11)
  - University of Virginia Police Department 1998-1999 (Box-folder 38:12)
  - Wide Awake 1992-1995 (Box-folder 38:13)
    pulled from files of Ronald J. Stump and Michele Samuels
  - Wide Awake--Amicus Brief by Attorney General 1994-1995 (Box-folder 38:14)
  - Wide Awake Appellate Brief 1992 (Box-folder 38:15)
  - Wide Awake Briefs--Appeals Court 1992-1994 (Box-folder 38:16)
  - Wide Awake--Brief for Respondents in Opposition to Petition for Writ of Certiorari 1994 (Box-folder 38:17)
  - Wide Awake Brief in the Supreme Court 1994-1995 (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Wide Awake Case Background Information 1991-1995 (Box-folder 39:2)
  - Wide Awake Productions vs. University of Virginia 1991-1995 (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Wide Awake--Rosenberger vs. Rector and Visitors 1991-1994 (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Wide Awake--University of Virginia Brief on Wide Awake 1991 (Box-folder 39:5)
  - Wide Awake--University of Virginia Motion for Summary Judgment in Wide Awake Productions Case 1990-1991 (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Wide Awake--University Response to Plaintiffs Request for Damages 1991-1996 (Box-folder 39:7)
  - Work in Progress--Grounds for Discussion 2000 (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Work in Progress--Peer Advising and Family Network--Early Move-Ins 1999-2000 (Box-folder 40:2)